[{"answer": "Unprecedented in large cases, normal in almost everyday cases, I have to point that out.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "The big question everyone is asking, why did you waive Jerry Sandusky's rights to have this hearing today?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "We have.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "You've taken a big gamble, haven't you, in removing your client's right to have all that?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Are you a pedophile?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Am I sexually attracted to underage boys?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Taken in a vacuum, I can't disagree with you.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "I mean, do you see to, again, an impartial observer just how awful that sounded?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "I do think it's strange behavior for a man of that age.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "ORGAN: But tell me this, when you hear a man of Jerry Sandusky's age talking about having horseplay with naked 10, 11, 12- year-old boys in showers, don't you think to yourself, this is very, very strange behavior for a man of that age?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "If you were prosecuting this, given the sheer wealth of allegations and the volume of people making them, would you feel pretty confident of at least some form of conviction here?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "I believe I'm coming forth to help children, to give them the courage to talk.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Let me ask you first, Bobby, why have you done this?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "That is true.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "Was the real problem here, as it seems to have been at Penn State as well that these kind of coaches at college level in America are put on to this kind of god- like plinth, you know, they're almost untouchable, and they start to believe they're untouchable?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, because Coach Boeheim was the coach of -- and is the coach of the Syracuse men's basketball team.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Why go after him?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Too little, too late, Piers.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Does that apology make any difference to you?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "The statute of limitations does apply in New York to bar Mike and Bobby from any criminal case prosecution of Mr. Fine.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "That's not for me to say.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Do you think that Jim Boeheim, given what he's said about you guys -- do you think he should be fired, given he's now tried to retract his comments?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "I think they do feel like that, in a sense.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Do you think this goes back to that sense of they're just to powerful to touch these guys?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "I appreciate the fact that you indicated to your audience that I'm not terribly objective.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "What do you make of the way this race is now unraveling as we head towards Iowa?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "First of all, I like Jon Huntsman, too, which probably isn't going to do Jon Huntsman any good in the Republican party.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Who would you rather President Obama face, when push comes to shove?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "First of all, I wouldn't say I self-imploded.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "How does he avoid the banana skin?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Well, it's very colorful, obviously.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "What did you make of that comment?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "Look, that's what's got us into Iraq, go in and blow everything apart.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Should America just allow this drone, with all of the technology, to be sitting there in Iranian hands?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "Well, there are 3,400 men and women at Camp Ashram, which is about 60 miles northeast of Baghdad, surrendered their means of self-protection to the United States Army in 2003 and 2004.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "What can you tell me about that?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, every time we go to the U.N. to try to get a sanction, we -- they end up building a couple more centrifuges.", "docId": "111213pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "In simple terms, how should the president deal with Iran?", "qSentId": 534}]